Guide to the Rice University Association of Rice Alumni records, 1922-2019 UA 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Association of Rice Alumni records
1922-2019
1970-1984
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Unknown
UA 003
31 Linear Feet 30 boxes
This collection contains records and items related to the Association of Rice Alumni. It includes records and meeting minutes of various alumni committees and boards.
Historical Note
"The purpose of the Association of Rice Alumni (ARA) is to provide the means of a continuing relationship between the university and its former students.
The association strives to stimulate intellectual and social participation of all members of the ARA, and to enable them to contribute to and share in the enhancement of the university. In addition, the association endeavors to foster deeper concern among its members for the welfare of the university, to strengthen the bond of understanding between the university and the community, to encourage gifts, to attract outstanding students and faculty, and to contribute toward maintaining Rice as a university in keeping with the ideals and aims of its founder.
The Association of Rice Alumni (ARA) is governed by the ARA Board in conjunction with the Office of Alumni Affairs."
(Quoted from alumni.rice.edu/about_alumassoc.html, accessed July 25, 2011)
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records and items related to the Association of Rice Alumni. It includes records and meeting minutes of various alumni committees and boards.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research, except where noted.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Acquisition Information
The items in this collection were donated or transferred to Woodson Research Center at various times between 1980 and 2019. Additional accruals are expected.
Separated Materials
Sports and special event clothing items donated by Rice alumni have been removed from this collection and are now located in UA 392.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Universities and colleges
Document Types
documents; oral histories (document genres)
Places
Rice University
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University
- Series I. Alumni Interviews
  - Oral History Interviews, Rice Alumni (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts of Taped Interviews (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Hubert (Gertrude) Bray (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Dr. Hubert Bray (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Gaylord Johnson (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Malcolm Lovett (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Stayton Nunn (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Transcripts of taped interview of Malcolm Lovett interviewed by the Junior League of Houston, July 27, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Interviews Tapes
    - Dr. Hubert Bray interviewed by Ray Hoagland (1/2), Oct. 21, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4, Cassette 1)
    - Dr. Hubert Bray interviewed by Ray Hoagland (2/2), Oct. 21, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4, Cassette 2)
    - Elwyn Simmons, Nov. 19, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4, Cassette 3)
    - Henry A. Tillett interviewed by Liz Williams, Dec. 23, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4, Cassette 4)
    - [Mrs. Hubert] Gertrude Bray interviewed by Ray Hoagland, Jan. 22, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5, Cassette 1)
    - Lel Red Interviewed by Doris Anderson, Jan. 6, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5, Cassette 2)
    - Elva Kalb Dumas interviewed by Debbie Walkman, Aug. 7, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5, Cassette 3)
    - Stayton Nunn interviewed by Ray Hoagland (1/2), April 12, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5, Cassette 4)
    - Stayton Nunn interviewed by Ray Hoagland (2/2), April 12, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6, Cassette 1)
    - Gaylord Johnson interviewed by Ray Hoagland (1/2), Dec. 6, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6, Cassette 2)
    - Gaylord Johnson interviewed by Ray Hoagland (2/2), Dec. 6, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6, Cassette 3)
    - Malcolm Lovett interviewed by Ray Hoagland, July 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6, Cassette 4)
    - Lel Red interviewed by Ray Hoagland, May 3, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7, Cassette 1)
    - Westerfield interviewed by Ray Hoagland (Box 1, Folder 7, Cassette 2)
    - Tapes of Distinguished Alumni, May 11,1985 (Box 1, Folder 7, Cassette 3)
- Series II. Executive Board
  - Constitution and By-laws
    - Notebook: Incorporated Papers, original Constitution, Revision and By-laws, Constitutional Redraft and Ammendments (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Constitution and By-laws--Mr Ballew's Proposed Changes (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Constitution and By-laws--Further Revisions (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Constitution and By-laws--Mr. Ballew (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Brief History (1st Constitution and Minutes of 1st Meeting), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board Member Photographs, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Charter and First Minutes, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes
    - Minutes, 1919-1953; Original Constitution and 1940 redraft (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1954-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1960s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1970-1974 (1/2) (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1970-1974 (2/2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1979-1984 (1/2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1979-1984 (2/2) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of the Executive Board, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Correspondence
    - Correspondence: Bill Ballew, John Evans, John Heard, Charles Moser (1/2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Bill Ballew, John Evans, John Heard, Charles Moser (2/2) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Frank Dent, David Farnsworth, and Henry Gissell (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Carolyn Wallace, 1974-1976 (1/2) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Carolyn Wallace, 1974-1976 (2/2) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Carolyn Wallace, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Pre 1970-1976 (1/2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Pre 1970-1976 (2/2) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (1/2) (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (2/2) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence--Board and Misc., 1989-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board Directories (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Board Notebook
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1988-89, 1989-90 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1990-1991 (1/2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1990-1991 (2/2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1994-1995 (1/2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1994-1995 (2/2) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1995-1996 (1/2) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1995-1996 (2/2) (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1996-1997 (1/2) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1996-1997 (2/2) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1997-1998 (1/2) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1997-1998 (2/2) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1998-1999 (1/2) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1998-1999 (2/2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ARA Board Notebook, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Board Sample Letters (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Board Calendars, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Permanent Officers Rosters (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mission Statement Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ARA Board Workshop, July 25, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ARA Board Workshop, August 11, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Trustees Governance (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Board, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Board, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Board--General (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Series III. Committees
  - Alumni Committees, 1990-1991 (1/2) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Committees, 1990-1991 (2/2) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1985-1986, 1988-1989, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Committee Club Handbooks, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Committee Appointments, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Committee Directory, 1974-75 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Committee Descriptions (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Committee Reports, 1924-1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Committee Rosters (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Committee Chair Notebook, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Committees, 1989-? (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Admissions Committee
    - Admissions Committee Correspondence, 1960-1974 (1/2) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Admissions Committee Correspondence, 1960-1974 (2/2) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Admissions Committee Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Admissions Committee Papers, 1978-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ad-Hoc 50 Year Anniversary Committee
    - Ad-Hoc 50th Anniversary Committee Papers, 1962 (1/2) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Ad-Hoc 50th Anniversary Committee Papers, 1962 (2/2) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ad-Hoc Alumni Institute Committee
    - Ad-Hoc Alumni Institute Committee Papers, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee on Satellite Business Organization, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ad-Hoc Review Committee (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Archives Committee
    - Archives Committee, 1975-1978, 1981-1983, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Archives Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Archives Committee, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Archives Committee Papers, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Area Club Committee
    - Area Clubs--Campus Reports (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Area Club Correspondence--General, 1956-1974 (1/3) (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Area Club Correspondence, Area Club Lists, Florida to Los Angeles, 1956-1974 (2/3) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Area Club Correspondence, Massachusetts to Washington D.C., 1956-1974 (3/3) (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Area Club Correspondence, California to Tennessee, Prior to 1971 (1/2) (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Area Club Correspondence, California to Tennessee, Prior to 1971 (2/2) (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Area Club Correspondence, Texas to Washington, 1962-1972 (1/2) (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Area Club Correspondence, Texas to Washington, 1962-1972 (2/2) (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Area Club Correspondence (General), 1967-1974 (1/2) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Area Club Correspondence (General), 1967-1974 (2/2) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Area Club Correspondence, California to Conroe, Texas, 1971-1972 (1/2) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Area Club Correspondence, California to Conroe, Texas, 1971-1972 (2/2) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Area Club Correspondence (General), 1974-1975 (1/2) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Area Club Correspondence (General), 1974-1975 (2/2) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Area Club Correspondence, California to Wisconsin, 1972-1973 (1/2) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Area Club Correspondence, California to Wisconsin, 1972-1973 (2/2) (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Area Club Correspondence, 1971-1972 (1/1) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Area Clubs Correspondence, 1971-1972 (2/3) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Area Clubs Correspondence, 1971-1972 (3/3) (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Area Clubs Correspondence, 1973-1977 (1/3) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Area Clubs Correspondence, 1973-1977 (2/3) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Area Clubs Correspondence, 1973-1977 (3/3) (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Area Club Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Area Clubs, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Area Clubs, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Area Clubs Handbooks (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Area Clubs, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Area Clubs, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Area Clubs, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Area Clubs--General (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Arts Committee
    - Arts Committee Papers, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Arts Committee Papers, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Athletics Committee
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on Athletics, 1980-1981 (1/2) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on Athletics, 1980-1981 (2/2) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Athletic Committee Correspondence and Trips, 1965-1974 (1/2) (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Athletic Committee Correspondence and Trips, 1965-1974 (2/2) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Athletic Committee Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Athletics--Stadium Dinner, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Athletics--Sugar Bowl, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Athletics--Blue Gray Game, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Athletics--Basketball, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Athletics--Notre Dame Game, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Athletics--Texas Pre-game Football, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Athletics--Blue Gray Scrimmage, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Athletics, 1974-1976, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Athletics, 1978-1979, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Athletics, 80's and 90's (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Athletics, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Athletics, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Athletics, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Athletics, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Athletics, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Athletics, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Athletics, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Athletics, 1987-1988, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Athletics, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Athletics, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Athletics, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Athletics, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Athletics, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Athletics--General (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Budget Committee
    - Budget Committee Accounts, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Budget Committee Correspondence, 1968-1974 (1/2) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Budget Committee Correspondence, 1968-1974 (2/2) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Budget Committee Operating Fund, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Education Committee
    - Subcommittees of the Education Committee: Arts, 1971-1974 (1/3) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Subcommittees of the Education Committee: Arts, 1971-1974 (2/3) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Subcommittees of the Education Committee: Arts, 1971-1974 (3/3) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Subcommittees of the Education Committee: Faculty-Alumni Liaison and Housing, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Subcommittee of the Education Committee: Rice Alumni Institute, Prior to 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Subcommittee of the Education Committee: Rice Alumni Institute, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Subcommittees of the Education Committee: Rice Employment by Alumni Program, 1970-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Subcommittee of the Education Committee: Senior Day, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Subcommittees of the Educations Committee: Spring Think, Prior to 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Subcommittee of the Education Committee: Spring Think, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Subcommittee of the Education Committee: Spring Think, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Subcommittee of the Education Committee: Student Alumni Liaison (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Education Committee Correspondence, 1970-1974 (1/2) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Education Committee Correspondence, 1970-1974 (2/2) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Education Committee Papers, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Education Committee Papers, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Education Committee Papers (General) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee
    - Executive Committee Papers, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Papers, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - History Committee
    - Rice University History Committee, 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Photocopies of index cards noting contributions to Alumni History Committee by Rice Alumni, 1965-1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Homecoming Committee
    - Homecoming: Frontier Five, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, Prior to 1970 (1/4) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, Prior to 1970 (2/4) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, Prior to 1970 (3/4) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, Prior to 1970 (4/4) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Homecoming Commitete Papers, 1971 (1/2) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1971 (2/2) (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1972 (1/2) (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1972 (2/2) (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1973 (1/2) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1973 (2/2) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1975 (1/2) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1975 (2/2) (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1976 (1/2) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1976 (2/2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1977 (1/2) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1977 (2/2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1978 (1/2) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1978 (2/2) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1979 (1/2) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1979 (2/2) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1980 (1/2) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1980 (2/2) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Homecoming Committee Papers (General) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Honors Committee
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Honors Committee Meeting Records, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Honors Committee Papers, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Honors Committee Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Honors Committee Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Honors Committee Papers, 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Honors Committee Papers, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Honors and Awards Committee Papers (General) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Long Range Planning Committee
    - Long Range Planning Committee Papers, 1989-1990 (1/3) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Long Range Planning Committee Papers, 1989-1990 (2/3) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Long Range Planning Committee Papers, 1989-1990 (3/3) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee Papers, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Planning Committee Papers (General) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee
    - Membership Committee Papers, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Nomination of the Alumni Governor Commitee
    - Alumni Governor Elections, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Governor Elections, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Governor Elections, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Governor Elections, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Governor Elections, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Governor Elections, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Governor Elections, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Board Elections, 1988-2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Board Elections, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Board Elections, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Nomination of the Executive Board Committee
    - Executive Board Elections, Prior to 1967 (1/2) (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Executive Board Elections, Prior to 1967 (2/2) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1970s, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Elections, 1989-2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board Election Correspondence, 1967-1974 (1/2) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board Election Correspondence, 1967-1974 (2/2) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Publications Committee
    - Publications Committee Papers, 1968-1974 (1/2) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Publications Committee Papers, 1968-1974 (2/2) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Publications Committee Papers, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Publications Committee Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Publications Committee Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Publications Committee Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Publications Committee Papers, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rice Clubs Committee Papers, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Rice Alumni Board of Representatives
    - Rice Alumni Board of Representatives Papers, 1958-1977 (1/3) (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Rice Alumni Board of Representatives Papers, 1958-1977 (2/3) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Rice Alumni Board of Representatives Papers, 1958-1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee
    - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee Papers, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee Papers, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Student-Alumni Liaison Committee Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Career Advisor's Directory, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Young Alumni Committee
    - Young Alumni Committee Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Young Alumni Committee Papers, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Young Alumni Committee Papers, 1991-1996 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Young Alumni Committee Papers, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Series IV. Events and Programs
  - 33 Million Dollar Campaign, circa 1967 (1/2) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 33 Million Dollar Campaign, circa 1967 (2/2) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Alumni College Program, 1995-2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Groups Papers, 1997-2000 (1/2) (Box 13, Folder 4)